[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed The Princess Bride?", "correct_answer": "Rob Reiner", "incorrect_answers": ["Christopher Guest", "Ron Howard", "Tony Scott"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement about the atmosphere Mars is true?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["It is quite dusty.", "It is relatively thin.", "It contains methane."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the names Paul, Paula, Paulina, Pablo, Paulo, Paolo?", "correct_answer": "Small, humble", "incorrect_answers": ["Sacred, hallowed", "Gtreat", "Stubborn, obstinate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie What About Bob?, what does Bob have around his neck when he is riding the bus to Lake Winnipesaukee in New Hampshire ?", "correct_answer": "his goldfish Gil in a jar", "incorrect_answers": ["some anti-bacterial soap", "his lucky rabbits foot", "some garlic cloves in a bottle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Former Emperor of Japan, Hirohito, was considered an expert in which of these subjects?", "correct_answer": "Marine biology", "incorrect_answers": ["Poetry", "Astronomy", "Linguistics"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This island, located in the Caribbean Sea, is the largest island of an archipelago called Greater Antilles. The city of Havana is located on it.", "correct_answer": "Cuba", "incorrect_answers": ["Hispaniola", "Haiti", "Jamaica"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is James Bonds female ally, in A View to a Kill, who helps him discover the villain\u2019s real purpose?", "correct_answer": "Stacey Sutton", "incorrect_answers": ["Doris Pritchard", "Carolyn Leach", "Kim Faraday"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What city in Eastern Europe, often associated with the story of Dracula, is also famous for Revolution Square, which was the site of a 1989 revolt?", "correct_answer": "Bucharest", "incorrect_answers": ["Warsaw", "Budapest", "Prague"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During what medical procedure can the so-called Korotkoff sounds be perceived?", "correct_answer": "Taking blood pressure", "incorrect_answers": ["Examining bowel movements", "All of these", "Ultrasound examination of the fetus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of meal is the traditional Chinese Zha jiang mian dish?", "correct_answer": "Noodle dish", "incorrect_answers": ["Fish soup", "Ice cream dessert", "Pork meatballs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the device used to measure the mass of atoms?", "correct_answer": "Mass spectrometer", "incorrect_answers": ["Submolecular weighter", "Atomometer", "Mass detector"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A regular fair  pair of  dice is rolled. What is the probability that the role  will be a 7?", "correct_answer": "1 in 6", "incorrect_answers": ["7 in 6", "6 in 7", "7 in 36"]}]